you guys look good you look happy some
of you look a little confused
some of you were looking at me like that
girl is ugly keep staring I get cuter I
am so happy to be here my tribe are
special life I've done a lot of research
so I I want to adhere to all the Drybar
rules I want you to know what I prepared
for you tonight I'm doing my full set
start to finish I have cut nothing in
conclusion I just like to say drive safe
you guys have been awesome - there see
what I did there all right now this is
fantastic the Drybar people are so
fabulous they put the comedian's up a
lot of clubs are cheap and give you
nothing it's very expensive on the road
I'd have to tell you guys just for fun
last time I checked into a Marriott went
to the desk clerk told them I wanted
something quiet and relaxing under $30
they gave me an ambien and a yoga mat
how's you do a lot of driving
so I've recently upgraded my car stereo
it is the greatest thing in the world it
is now voice-activated satellite radio
it's a it's not Siri it's not Alexa but
if you're in my car right now and you
say jazz you might hear Miles Davis yeah
yeah right okay you say rock you might
hear van Halen all right good so I'm
driving through Los Angeles this guy and
a big red Hummer cuts me off like a
idiot and it switches to the news don't
worry this is not where it's gonna get
all weird and political I promise you
that although it is difficult being a
stand-up comic nowadays and not at least
making a little fun of the way the
president looks no matter what side
you're on we can all agree
he's got odd coloring for a human being
I'm pretty sure Donald Trump snorts tang
because orange lives matter too doesn't
he look like he's always just taking a
big handful of Sour Patch Kids
everybody's wrong with me and the hair
everybody talks about Donald Trump's
hair I have figured out the deal with
Donald Trump's hair he has got a cotton
candy machine at home
I know I'm the last person that she'd be
talking about anybody's hair
hey did you know Drybar comedy has their
own app download it right now to watch
save and share clips and watch my whole
special